evirtualguru.com 2016-11-19

# Complete Privacy Policy for www.evirtualguru.com

**For www.eVirtualGuru.com**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at evirtualguru@gmail.com .

At www.evirtualguru.com , the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.evirtualguru.com  and how it is used.

**• eVirtualguru.com Complete Privacy Policy**

You should read our privacy policy if you are:

• a student;

• a parent or guardian;

• a child care provider;

• a principal or teacher;

• an academic or researcher;

• a participant in a program or service delivered by us;

• a person seeking employment with us;

• any other individual whose personal information we may collect or hold. **Information we collect and why we use it**

We are responsible for provide Educational material that help all the students from all over the world access quality and affordable childcare; early childhood education; school education; post-school, higher education; international education and academic research, through: • efficient national program management; • effective working relationships with non-government education authorities and providers, universities and other providers of community groups and other stakeholders; Generally, we collect personal information in order to properly and efficiently carry out one or more of our functions. We only use personal information for the purpose(s) for which it was given to us and for directly related purposes (unless otherwise required or authorised by or under law); as consented to by you or if a permitted general situation exists.

**Privacy Notices** In addition to our privacy policy, we may need to explain specific privacy practices in more detail at other times. In such circumstances we develop and provide separate privacy notices to describe how we will handle the personal information that we collect. For example, where we ask you to provide personal information in relation to a particular program that we administer, we will provide you with a privacy notice at the time of collection or as soon as practicable afterwards, which details our personal information handling practices in relation to that particular program.

**Personal Information Holdings** We maintain, on an ongoing basis, a Personal Information Holdings document that explains the various types of personal information we collect and hold, what the information is used for and the third parties to whom the information is normally disclosed. Where applicable, the document also details where we are authorised to collect, use or disclose information under legislation relevant to our policies, programs and services.

**Electronic Communication** There are inherent risks associated with the transmission of information over the internet, including via email. You should be aware of this when sending personal information to us via email or via our website or social media platforms. If this is of concern to you then you may use other methods of communication with us, such as post, fax or telephone (although these also have risks associated with them). We only record your email address when you send a message to us or subscribe to one of our mailing lists. Any personal information, including email addresses, will only be used or disclosed for the purpose for which it was provided.

**Log  Files** Like many other Web sites, www.evirtualguru.com, makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons  ** www.evirtualguru.com, does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. A cookie is a small file containing a string of characters to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. It is information that your web browser sends back to our website server whenever you visit it again. We use cookies to ‘remember’ your browser between page visits.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie** .:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.evirtualguru.com .:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.evirtualguru.com, and other sites on the Internet. .:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include …. **Google Adsense**

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.evirtualguru.com, send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.evirtualguru.com, has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.evirtualguru.com privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**Google Analytics** We use Google Analytics to collect information about visitors to our website. Google Analytics uses first-party cookies and JavaScript code to help analyse how users use the site. It anonymously tracks how visitors interact with this website, including how they have accessed the site (for example from a search engine, a link, an advertisement) and what they did on the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purposes of compiling reports on website activity and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser.

**Links to External Websites** Our website includes links to other websites. We are not responsible for the content and privacy practices of other websites. We recommend that you examine each website’s Privacy Policy separately.

**Data Quality** We take all reasonable steps to make sure that the personal information we collect and store is accurate, up-to-date, complete, relevant and not misleading.

**Complaints** If you think we may have breached your privacy you may contact us to make a complaint using the contact details below. In order to ensure that we fully understand the nature of your complaint and the outcome you are seeking, we prefer that you make your complaint in writing. . **Contact Us** If you have any enquiries or complaints about privacy, or if you wish to access or correct your personal information, please email us at evirtualguru@gmail.com or  contact@evirtualguru.com or click _[Contact Us](http://evirtualguru.com/about/contact-us/)_

**Changes to this privacy policy** Please note that the privacy policy may change from time to time. Last updated: 16 July, 2015
